A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Jobs, 1
  - 938 - Sesame Street, 1995 March (Box 61, Folder 939)
    Photographer: Andrew Lichtenstein. Spring 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 939 - Palestinian Women, 1995 March (Box 62, Folder 940)
    Photographer: Rula Halawani. Spring 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 940 - Growing Up Not a Child, 1995 March (Box 62, Folder 941)
    Photographer: Michael Felder. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 941 - Street Soldiers, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 942)
    Photographer: Jim Dennis. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 942 - Different and the Same - Martin Luther King Jr. School, Pittsburgh, 1995 Spring (Box 62, Folder 943)
    Photographer: Lynn Johnson. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 943 - QUASAR Math Project, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 944)
    Photographer: Fred LeBlanc
  - 944 - Mexican Human Rights Academy Office, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 945)
    Photographer: Robert Fox
  - 945 - Chiapas, Mexico, 1994 September (Box 62, Folder 946)
    Photographer: Antonio Turok. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 947 - Ford Foundation, Chile Field Office, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 947)
    Photographer: Marcelo Montecino. 1994 FF Annual Report.
    Chile
  - 948 - Ford Foundation, India Field Office, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 948)
    Photographer: Asem Ansari. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 949 - Ford Foundation, Bangladesh Field Office, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 949)
    1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 950 - Youthbuild - Urban Poverty, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 950)
    Photographer: Richard Howard. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 951 - Urban Trust, South Africa, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 951)
    Photographer: Markus Weiss. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 952 - Paa Ya Paa Gallery, Korogocho Slum Artists, Kenya, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 952)
    Photographer: Wendy Stone. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 953 - Womens Health Action and Research Unit (WHARU), 1994 (Box 62, Folder 953)
    Photographer: Slim Akeh. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 954 - COWAN - Country Women Association of Nigeria, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 954)
  - 956 - GA Sec of State - Motor Voter Law, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 955)
    Photographer: Andy Bowen. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 957 - Kenya Rural Enterprise Program, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 956)
  - 958 - Campfire, Zimbabwe, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 957)
  - 959 - Mobilization Against Desertification, Kenya, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 958)
  - 960 - Kenya Anti Rape Organization, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 959)
  - 961 - Childrens Action Alliance, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 960)
    Photographer: Jeffrey Scott. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 962 - African Network for the Prevention and Protection Against Child Abuse and Neglect (ANPPCAN), 1994 (Box 63, Folder 961)
  - 963 - Roma Photoshoot, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 962)
    Photographer: Peter Korniss. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 964 - Voting Rights Conference, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 963)
    Photographer: Grant LeDuck. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 965 - Voices of Illinois Children, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 964)
    Photographer: Marc PoKempner. 1994 FF Annual Report.
  - 966 - Vietnam Women, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 965)
    Photographer: Radhika Chalasani
  - 967 - South Africa, land reform, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 966)
    Photographer: Andrew Bannister
  - 968 - New Community Corporation, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 967)
    Photographer: Donna Binder. Spring 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 969 - Phoenix Industries, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 968)
    Photographer: Woit, Steve 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 970 - Land Reform in Philippines, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 969)
    Photographer: Edwin Tuyay
  - 971 - Supportive Housing, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 970)
    Photographer: Andrew Lichtenstein. Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 972 - Supportive Housing in Minneapolis, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 971)
    Photographer: Terry Gydeson. Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 973 - Project Quest, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 972)
    Photographer: Jeffrey Scott. Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
    San Antonio, Texas
  - 974 - Lawyers Comm. For Civil Rights Law - Recent Grants, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 973)
    Photographer: Richard Bloom. Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 975 - Community Development Corporation (CDC) Partnerships, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1995 July (Box 64, Folder 974)
    Photographer: Lynn Johnson
  - 976 - Galling Pook Awards, with President Fidel V. Ramos, Philippines, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 975)
  - 979 - Marikina River, Manila, Philippines, and Bulacan Cultural Festival, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 976)
    Photographer: Lito Menor
  - 980a - Innovations - Federal - Dept of Defense - National Defense on the Offense, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 977)
  - 980b - Innovations - Federal - Dept of the Interior - Reinvention of the Bureau of Reclamation, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 978)
  - 980c - Innovations - Federal - Dept of Labor - Early Warning Program, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 979)
  - 980d - Innovations - Federal - Dept of Defense - Ozone Depleting Chemical Elimination, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 980)
  - 980e - Innovations - Federal - Dept of Justice - Operation JOBs, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 981)
  - 980f - Innovations - Federal - Dept of Labor - Maine Top 200 Experimental Targeting Program, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 982)
  - 980g - Innovations - State and Local - Genesis: Healthy Young Families, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 983)
  - 980h - Innovations - State and Local - Hillsborough County, Florida, Health Care Plan, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 984)
  - 980i - Innovations - State and Local - Competition and Costing, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 985)
  - 980j - Innovations - State and Local - Citywork, Louisville, Kentucky, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 986)
  - 980k - Innovations - State and Local - Hamilton Terrace Learning Center, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 987)
  - 980L - Innovations - State and Local - Elderchoice, Massachusetts, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 988)
  - 980m - Innovations - State and Local - Center for Technology, New York State, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 989)
  - 980n - Innovations - State and Local - The Civil Enforcement Initiative, New York City, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 990)
  - 980o - Innovations - State and Local - Project Quest, San Antonio, Texas, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 991)
  - 981 - Project Quest, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 992)
    Photographer: Stephen Shames. Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 982 - Street Soldiers, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 993)
    Photographer: Mark Ludak. Spring 1996 FF 'Report'.
  - 983 - Indochina Arts Project - Cultural Preservation Grant, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 994)
    Summer/Fall 1995 FF 'Report'.
  - 984 - Tri-Link Inc., 1995 (Box 65, Folder 995)
    Photographer: Jeff Mitchell. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 985 - Mercy Housing, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 996)
    Photographer: Leena Histanen. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 986 - Campus Diversity, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 997)
    Photographer: Andrew Lichtenstein. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 987 - Networks for School Renewal, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 998)
    Photographer: Alex Kirkbride. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 988 - Nigerian Community Development Trust Fund, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 999)
    Photographer: Slim Akeh. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 989A - Paa Yaa Paa Gallery, Korogocho Slum artists, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1000)
    Photographer: Wendy Stone
  - 989B - Legal Advice Centre, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1001)
  - 989C - Anti-Rape Organization, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1002)
  - 989D - Undugu Society, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1003)
  - 989E - Rural Enterprise Program, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1004)
  - 989F - AIDS Society, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1005)
  - 989G - Progress for Women, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1006)
  - 989H - Women Finance Trust, Kenya, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1007)
  - 990A - Poland (various grantees), 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1008)
    Photographer: Sean Sprague
  - 990B - Czech Republic (various grantees), 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1009)
    Czech Republic
  - 990C - Russia (various grantees), 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1010)
  - 992 - Thailand Fisheries, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1011)
    Photographer: Hollyman, Stephanie. 1995 FF Annual Report.
  - 993 - Thailand - Palm Sugar Occupation Project/Friends of Women Foundation, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1012)
  - 994 - Women's Health Coalition, Fisheries/Tangail, Center for Natural Resources, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1013)
  - 995 - Forestry in Thailand, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1014)
  - 996 - United Nations Fourth World Conference on Women, Beijing, China, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1015)
    Beijing, China
  - Negatives, 20 box(es)
    Arrangement
    Negatives are arranged numerically, by the Job file number.
    - Jobs 1 - 15 (Box 111)
    - Jobs 16 - 67 (Box 112)
    - Jobs 68 - 100 (Box 113)
    - Jobs 101 - 155 (Box 114)
    - Jobs 156 - 180 (Box 115)
    - Jobs 181 - 224 (Box 116)
    - Jobs 225 - 277 (Box 117)
    - Jobs 278 - 311 (Box 118)
    - Jobs 312 - 356 (Box 119)
    - Jobs 357 - 374 (Box 120)
    - Jobs 375 - 430 (Box 121)
    - Jobs 432 - 464 (Box 122)
    - Jobs 465 - 495 (Box 123)
    - Jobs 496 - 520 (Box 124)
    - Jobs 521 - 543 (Box 125)
    - Jobs 544 - 566 (Box 126)
    - Jobs 621 - 644, 662 (Box 127)
    - Jobs 729 - 790 (Box 128)
    - Jobs 791 - 827h (Box 129)
    - Jobs 832 - 858, 864 - 878 (Box 130)
    - Unidentified Negatives (Box 131)
      Mostly 4x5 black and white negatives and color transparencies, without identifying captions.
- Ford Foundation Trustees, Officers, and Staff Photographs, 2
  - Ford Foundation Officers Meeting, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 1035)
  - Ford Foundation Officers Meetings, 1970s (Box 70, Folder 1036)
  - Ford Motor Company Archive files - Henry Ford, Edsel Ford (Box 70, Folder 1037)
  - Ford Foundation Directors/Officers Meetings, 1980s-1990s (Box 70, Folder 1038)
  - Ford Foundation - Office of Reports - Architectural photographs of Ford Foundation Headquarters, 1960s (Box 70, Folder 1039)
  - Ford Foundation - Office of Reports Staff, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 1040)
  - Ford Foundation Program Assistants, grouped by Program Area, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 1041)
  - Ford Foundation Program Assistants, 1996-1998 (Box 70, Folder 1042)
  - Ford Foundation Officers Meeting, 1978 November (Box 70, Folder 1043)
  - Ford Foundation Trustees, Directors, Associate Directors meeting, 1950s (Box 70, Folder 1044)
    Includes Henry Ford II, Paul Hoffman, Chester Davis, Robert Hutchins, and H. Rowan Gaither.
  - Mark W. Abrams (Box 70, Folder 1045)
  - Frederick L. Allen (Box 70, Folder 1046)
  - R. Anderson (Box 70, Folder 1047)
  - James W. Armsey (Box 70, Folder 1048)
  - Verne S. Atwater (Box 70, Folder 1049)
  - Paul Balaran, 1990 February (Box 70, Folder 1050)
  - Stephen Davison Bechtel, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 1051)
  - Edgar Beckham (Box 70, Folder 1052)
  - David E. Bell, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1053)
  - George Benson (Box 70, Folder 1054)
  - Alison Bernstein (Box 70, Folder 1055)
  - Susan V. Berresford, President, 1996 March (Box 71, Folder 1056)
  - Susan V. Berresford (V.P. Program Division), 1992 (Box 71, Folder 1057)
  - Susan V. Berresford: V.P.: Program Division, 1989 June (Box 71, Folder 1058)
  - Susan V. Berresford (Box 71, Folder 1059)
  - Sheila Biddle (Box 71, Folder 1060)
  - Richard M. Bissell, Jr. (Box 71, Folder 1061)
  - Patricia Biggers (Box 71, Folder 1062)
  - Eugene R. Black (Box 71, Folder 1063)
  - James B. Black (Box 71, Folder 1064)
  - Frederick M. Bohen, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1065)
  - Carl Borgmann (Box 71, Folder 1066)
  - Rodrigo Botero (Box 71, Folder 1067)
  - Dr. Frank Bowles (Box 71, Folder 1068)
  - Kieran M. Bracken, Comptroller (Box 71, Folder 1069)
  - Robert B. Braswell, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 1070)
  - Andrew F. Brimmer, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1071)
  - Dyke Brown (Box 72, Folder 1072)
  - James Brownlee (Box 72, Folder 1073)
  - George Bryant (Box 72, Folder 1074)
  - James W. Bryant (Box 72, Folder 1075)
  - McGeorge Bundy (President), 1974 November (Box 72, Folder 1076)
  - McGeorge Bundy (President), 1960s-1970s; 11x14 inches or larger.; Oversize prints. (Box 147, Folder 1998)
  - McGeorge Bundy (President), 1960s-1970s (Box 72, Folder 1077)
  - McGeorge Bundy (President), 1966 (Box 72, Folder 1078)
  - McGeorge Bundy (President) - Visit to New Delhi Field Office, India, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 1079)
  - Yvonne B. Burke (Trustee) (Box 72, Folder 1080)
  - John Calmore (Box 72, Folder 1081)
  - Frank Campsall (Box 72, Folder 1082)
  - William Carmichael: V.P. for Developing Countries Program (Box 72, Folder 1083)
  - Thomas H. Carroll (Box 72, Folder 1084)
  - Emmett Carson (Box 72, Folder 1085)
  - Harry Case (Box 72, Folder 1086)
  - Mariam Chamberlain, with Fred Crossland, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 1087)
  - Neil W. Chamberlain (Box 72, Folder 1088)
  - Earl F. Cheit (Box 72, Folder 1089)
  - Lilia Clemente, 1971 December (Box 72, Folder 1090)
  - Karl T. Compton (Box 72, Folder 1091)
  - Samuel DuBois Cook, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1092)
  - John Cowles (Box 72, Folder 1093)
  - B. Craig (Box 72, Folder 1094)
  - Fred Crossland (Box 72, Folder 1095)
  - Robert F. Culbertson (Box 72, Folder 1096)
  - Matthew J. Cullen, Jr., 1960 (Box 72, Folder 1097)
  - Merrimon Cuninggim, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1098)
  - Robert Curvin (Box 72, Folder 1099)
  - Edward F. D'Arms, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1100)
  - Donald K. David, Trustee (Box 72, Folder 1101)
  - David Davis, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 1102)
  - Peter E. DeJanosi (Box 73, Folder 1103)
  - Guilliame de Spoelbach (Box 73, Folder 1104)
  - William Diaz (Box 73, Folder 1105)
  - William Henry Donaldson, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1106)
  - Hedley Donovan, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 1107)
  - Howard Dressner, 1976 October; 1967 June (Box 73, Folder 1108)
  - Christopher Edley, 1967-1973 (Box 73, Folder 1109)
  - Robert H. Edwards, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1110)
  - Mark Elliot (Box 73, Folder 1111)
  - James R. Ellis, 1970 December (Box 73, Folder 1112)
  - John English (Box 73, Folder 1113)
  - Douglas Ensminger, 1954-1969 (Box 73, Folder 1114, 1115)
  - Mark F. Etheridge, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 1116)
  - Alvin C. Eurich, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 1117)
  - John Scott Everton, 1953-1957 (Box 73, Folder 1118)
  - Mario Fantini (Box 73, Folder 1119)
  - Allen Faurot (Box 73, Folder 1120)
  - Clarance Faust, 1956-1961 (Box 73, Folder 1121)
  - Marvin Feldman (Box 73, Folder 1122)
  - Frances Daly Ferguson, Trustee (Box 73, Folder 1123)
  - Paul B. Firstenberg, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1124)
  - Scott Fletcher, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 1125)
  - Benson Ford (Box 73, Folder 1126)
  - Henry Ford II (Box 73, Folder 1127)
  - Shepard Forman (Box 73, Folder 1128)
  - Melvin Fox (Box 73, Folder 1129)
  - Peter Fraenkel (Box 73, Folder 1130)
  - Fred W. Friendly, 1966; 1968; 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1131)
  - H. Rowan Gaither, Jr., 1957 (Box 74, Folder 1132)
  - H. Rowan Gaither, Jr. and Benson Ford at the Economic Club of Detroit, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1133)
  - Gaither Study Committee, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 1134)
  - George Gant (Box 74, Folder 1135)
  - Lloyd Garrison (Box 74, Folder 1136)
  - Nina G. Garsoian (Box 74, Folder 1137)
  - Peter Geithner (Box 74, Folder 1138)
  - John Gerhart (Box 74, Folder 1139)
  - Kermit Gordon, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1140)
  - Stanley Gordon (Box 74, Folder 1141)
  - William P. Gormbley Jr. (Box 74, Folder 1142)
  - Laurence M. Gould, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 1143)
  - Stanley W. Gregory (Box 74, Folder 1144)
  - George Griffiths, 1971 September (Box 74, Folder 1145)
  - Walter A. Haas, Jr., 1970 December (Box 74, Folder 1146)
  - Gladys Hardy, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 1147)
  - Oscar Harkavy, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1148)
  - Michael S. Harris (Box 74, Folder 1149)
  - Gordon Harrison, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1150)
  - Barbara Hatton (Box 74, Folder 1151)
  - Henry T. Heald, 1956; 1963 (Box 74, Folder 1152)
  - Alexander Heard (Box 74, Folder 1153)
  - Dr. Vivian W. Henderson, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 1154)
  - Antony Herrey (Box 75, Folder 1155)
  - Willard J. Hertz (Box 75, Folder 1156)
  - Dr. Forrest F. (Frosty) Hill, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 1157)
  - Paul G. Hoffman (Box 75, Folder 1158)
  - Sir Christopher Hogg (Box 75, Folder 1159)
  - John B. Howard (Box 75, Folder 1160)
  - Harold Howe (Box 75, Folder 1161)
  - David Hunter, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 1162)
  - James Ivy (Box 75, Folder 1163)
  - Sanford M. Jaffe (Box 75, Folder 1164)
  - Milton Katz (Box 75, Folder 1165)
  - Eamon Kelly, 1971 December (Box 75, Folder 1166)
  - Roger Kennedy, 1970; 1978 (Box 75, Folder 1167)
  - J. Donald Kingsley, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 1168)
  - Sigmund Koch (Box 75, Folder 1169)
  - John Koprowski (Box 75, Folder 1170)
  - Frances Korten (Box 75, Folder 1171)
  - Richard W. Lambourne (Box 75, Folder 1172)
  - Edwin H. Land (Box 75, Folder 1173)
  - Roy E. Larson (Box 75, Folder 1174)
  - Dr. Hugh Rodman Leavell (Box 75, Folder 1175)
  - Thomas H. Lenagh (Box 75, Folder 1176)
  - Robert D. Lilley, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 1177)
  - Clifford B. Longley (Box 75, Folder 1178)
  - John H. Loudon (Box 75, Folder 1179)
  - W. McNeil Lowry, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1180)
  - Richard Magat (Box 75, Folder 1181)
  - Dorothy Marshall, 1971 September (Box 75, Folder 1182)
  - Harvey B. Matthews, Jr. (Box 75, Folder 1183)
  - John J. McCloy (Box 75, Folder 1184)
  - Aubrey V. McCutcheon III (Box 75, Folder 1185)
  - Joseph M. McDaniel, Jr. (Box 75, Folder 1186)
  - Donald F. McHenry (Box 75, Folder 1187)
  - William McPeak (Box 75, Folder 1188)
  - Edward Meade (Box 76, Folder 1189)
  - Anita Miller, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 1190)
  - J. Irwin Miller, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 1191)
  - Paul F. Miller (Box 76, Folder 1192)
  - William G. Milliken (Box 76, Folder 1193)
  - Janice Molnar (Box 76, Folder 1194)
  - Charles Moore (Box 76, Folder 1195)
  - Malcolm C. Moos (Box 76, Folder 1196)
  - James L. Morrill (Box 76, Folder 1197)
  - David C. Mumford (Box 76, Folder 1198)
  - Lester Nelson (Box 76, Folder 1199)
  - James M. Nicely (Box 76, Folder 1200)
  - Waldemar A. Nielsen, 1961 May (Box 76, Folder 1201)
  - William H. Nims (Box 76, Folder 1202)
  - Luis G. Nogales (Box 76, Folder 1203)
  - Eugene Northrop, 1960-1969 (Box 76, Folder 1204)
  - Melvin Oliver (Box 76, Folder 1205)
  - Elizabeth Paschal, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 1206)
  - Benjamin Payton, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 1207)
  - Paul P. Pearson, 1960 July (Box 76, Folder 1208)
  - Donald S. Perkins (Box 76, Folder 1209)
  - William Pincus, 1966 April (Box 76, Folder 1210)
  - Barbara Scott Preiskel, Trustee (Box 76, Folder 1211)
  - Don K. Price Jr. (Box 76, Folder 1212)
  - Alan P. Pryce-Jones, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 1213)
  - Harriet Raab (Box 76, Folder 1214)
  - Marshall A. Robinson (Box 76, Folder 1215)
  - Henry Saltzman (Box 76, Folder 1216)
  - Judy Samuelson (Box 76, Folder 1217)
  - John Scanlon, 1963 December (Box 76, Folder 1218)
  - Howard G. Schaller, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 1219)
  - Joseph Schull (Box 76, Folder 1220)
  - Richard C. Sheldon (Box 76, Folder 1221)
  - Joseph Elliot Slater, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 1222)
  - Soedjatmoko, 1973 April 2 (Box 76, Folder 1223)
  - Edson W. Spencer, Trustee (Box 76, Folder 1224)
  - John M. Stalnaker (Box 76, Folder 1225)
  - Peter Stanley (Box 76, Folder 1226)
  - Clinton Stevenson (Box 76, Folder 1227)
  - Shepard Stone (Box 76, Folder 1228)
  - Dr. Julius A. Stratton (Box 77, Folder 1229)
  - Linda Strumpf, 1981; 1992 (Box 77, Folder 1230)
  - Francis X. Sutton - Deputy Vice President of the International Division, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1231)
  - Mitchell Sviridoff, 1970; 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1232)
  - Cleon O. Swayzee (Box 77, Folder 1233)
  - Howard Swearer, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1234)
  - Andrea Taylor (Box 77, Folder 1235)
  - Barron Tenny (Box 77, Folder 1236)
  - Franklin A. Thomas, 1977 June 29 (Box 77, Folder 1237)
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 1238)
    Photographer: Georgina Silk.
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1980 May 23 (Box 77, Folder 1239)
    Photographer: DeLucia.
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1987 (Box 77, Folder 1240)
    Photographer: T.T. Miller.
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1988 (Box 77, Folder 1241)
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1992 (Box 77, Folder 1242)
  - Franklin A. Thomas (President), 1995 (Box 77, Folder 1243)
    Photographer: Denny.
  - Robert Tolles (Box 77, Folder 1244)
  - D.L. Trautman, Jr., 1957 (Box 77, Folder 1245)
  - Lee Travers (Box 77, Folder 1246)
  - Tom Trebat (Box 77, Folder 1247)
  - Arthur D. Trottenberg, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 1248)
  - Ralph Tyler, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 1249)
  - Brian Urquhart (Box 77, Folder 1250)
  - Henry H. Villard, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 1251)
  - Anna Wadia (Box 77, Folder 1252)
  - Patricia Wald, 1971 September (Box 77, Folder 1253)
  - (Mary) Lynn Walker (Box 77, Folder 1254)
  - F. Champion Ward, 1957; 1966 (Box 77, Folder 1255)
  - Glenn E. Watts (Trustee), 1976 June (Box 78, Folder 1256)
  - James B. Weber, Jr. (Box 78, Folder 1257)
  - Bethuel M. Webster, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 1258)
  - G. Weinstock (Box 78, Folder 1259)
  - Av Weston, 1967 January 6 (Box 78, Folder 1260)
  - Carl M. White, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 1261)
  - Harry E. Wilhelm, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 1262)
  - Roger W. Wilkins, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1263)
  - G.E. Wilson (Box 78, Folder 1264)
  - Louis Winnick (Box 78, Folder 1265)
  - Geoffrey Wiseman (Box 78, Folder 1266)
  - Alfred C. Wolf, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 1267)
  - Eva Wollenberg (Box 78, Folder 1268)
  - Paul Woodring, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 1269)
  - Thomas H. Wyman, Trustee (Box 78, Folder 1270)
  - Charles E. Wyzanski, Jr. (Box 78, Folder 1271)
  - Paul Ylvisaker, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1272)
  - George Zeidenstein (Box 78, Folder 1273)
  - Peter Zimmerman, 1981; 1983 (Box 78, Folder 1274)
- General, Program, and Project Photographs, 3
  - Behavioral Sciences (BS), 3_1
    - Behavior Sciences Grants for Individual Research, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 1275)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, Stanford, CA, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 1276)
    - Gaustad Hospital - Research in Mental Health, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 1277)
    - Hampstead Child Therapy Course and Clinic, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 1278)
    - Tavistock Institute of Human Relations, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 1279)
    - University of Illinois - Dr. Julian Steward, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 1280)
    - University of Wisconsin - Individual Grants in Research - Primate Laboratory, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 1281)
    - Yerkes Laboratory of Primate Biology, Emory University, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 1282)
  - Economic Development and Administration (EDA), 3_2
    - American Friends Service Committee, Action and Research Program on Farm Labor Coops in California, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1283)
    - Brookings Institution, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1284)
    - Columbia University - Graduate School of Business, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1285)
    - Commission on Money and Credit, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1286)
    - Gordon-Howell Report on Business Education - Robert Aaron Gordon and James Edwin Howell, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1287)
    - Harvard Business School - Case Method Seminar, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 1288)
    - Harvard University - Research on Weapons Development and Acquisition, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1289)
    - Indiana University - Resident Labor Education Program, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1290)
    - Institute of Basic Mathematics, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1291)
    - Institute of International Education - Economics Institute at University of Colorado for Foreign Graduate Students in Economics, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1292)
    - University of Michigan - Study relating to Introduction of Technological Changes in the Transportation Industry, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1293)
    - Misc. photographs for Economic Development and Administration (EDA) booklet, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1294)
    - National Industrial Conference Board - Study of Negro Employment, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1295)
    - Retiring and Relocation of Unemployed Workers, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 1296)
    - Regional Faculty Seminars - Duke University, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 1297)
    - Stanford University Training Program for Business Teachers for Less-Developed Countries (ICAME), 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1298)
    - Texas Southern University - Business Programs, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 1299)